Guide to the Susie Bright papers and On Our Backs records, 1978-2013.
Bright, Susie papers and On Our Backs records
- On Our Backs
  - On Our Backs Photos and Miscellaneous
    - "Wrong Arm of the Law" (Box 24, Folder 48)
    - "Against All Bods" (Box 24, Folder 49)
    - "Twisted Sisters" (Box 24, Folder 50)
    - Susie Bright Photoshoot, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 51)
      By Julie Dennis, L.A. Color Labs; slides
    - Debi Sundahl and Myrna Elana photoshoot (Box 24, Folder 52)
    - Louise Smith and "Pauli Schell" (Box 24, Folder 53)
    - Nan and Debi Portraits (Box 24, Folder 54)
    - 1st S/M video made, ca. 1982-1983 (Box 24, Folder 55)
      Nan Kinney and Debi Sundahl, produced and shot by Lustry Lady
    - Portraits of Debi Sundahl, Myrna Elana, ca. 1982-1983 (Box 24, Folder 56)
      Taken by Ron Kent, Samois Era
    - 10th Anniversary Cover Shoot-Debi Sundahl (Box 24, Folder 57)
      negatives
    - Gay Day/Russian River, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 58)
      Photos
    - Nan and Debi shot by Jill Posener, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 59)
    - Green Door Premiere (Box 24, Folder 60)
      Photos of Mitchell B ros dancers getting ready for and attending the "Green Door 2" premiere. Peppar, nan, Debi, Susie, Honey, Ant Mitchell
    - Stormy Leather Catalog (Box 24, Folder 61)
      8"x10"s of Debi Sundahl's photoshoot
    - Debi Sundahl photoshoot, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 62)
    - Photo of Nan, Debi, Monika (Box 24, Folder 63)
    - X-mas, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 64)
      Phtos of Debi Sundahl, Nan Kinney and two friends around the Christmas Tree
    - Opera Plaza, ca. 1985 (Box 24, Folder 65)
      Photos of Nan Kinney, Debi Sundahl, Susie Bright, and Honey Lee
    - "Meltdown of a Stripper", ca. 1994 (Box 24, Folder 66)
      Never published photoshoot by East Bay photography, featuring Debi Sundahl
    - Mendocino (Box 24, Folder 67)
      Photos of Debi Sundahl and Nan Kinney
    - Big Sur, Malibu (Box 24, Folder 68)
    - Screening Party--PP:S (Box 24, Folder 69)
      Photos of friends
    - Croquet Picnic--The Foursome (Box 24, Folder 70)
      Phtoshoot--Debi Sundahl, Nan Kinney, ?, ?
    - Playboy TV, 1986-1987 (Box 24, Folder 71)
      Slides from "Sexcetera" series featuring Debi Sundahl at the O'Farrell Theater
    - H. L. Butch Pictorial--Nan (Box 24, Folder 72)
      "Born in USA" photoshoot. Nan posing with a car
    - Monica and Nan, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 73)
      Photos of trip to San Francisco for Virgn Machine
    - Gay Games II--Marathon (Box 24, Folder 74)
      Phto negatives
    - Hungry Hearts (Box 24, Folder 75)
      Photos of Debi Sundahl and promotional photos for Lesbian Erotic Video
    - "Stormy Leather" 1st Catalog + (5X7") (Box 24, Folder 76)
      On Our Backs "Stormy Leather" edition and 5X7"s
    - "Stormy Leather" (1st Catalog) (Box 24, Folder 77)
      "Leather for Women" photoshoot featuring Debi Sundahl and Kokomo Tise
    - Burlezk Live (Box 24, Folder 78)
      Flyer for the Southwest Tour; photo of co-ed tour flyers; photo of fan; original quarter-card featuring Shelley as Martin and Debi
    - P.R. Phtos for On Our Backs (Box 24, Folder 79)
      Photos of models, Debi Sundahl, Nan Kinney, staff, and friends
    - Shelley as martin (Box 24, Folder 80)
      Photos of Shelley posing as Matin with Debi Sundahl and a car
    - Burlezk Live, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 81)
      Film strip; black and white photonegatives; dancers: Ceraage, Ramona, Casie, Denisha, Nan, Debi, J. Fields Pubic Hair Design"
    - Burlezk Live, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 82)
      Film strip color photonegatives; dancers: Mitchell Brothers, Sandy, Peppar, Blake, Debi
    - Burlezk Live, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 83)
      Film strip photonegatives; dancers: Mitchell Brothers, Fallon,Blake, Linda Lioness
    - Burlezk Live, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 84)
      Film strip photonegatives
  - Items labeled as in Box 24B are housed in a smaller box inside of Box 24
    - Gordon and Sundahl, ca. 1992 (Box 24B, Folder 1)
      Photos of John Gordon (soundtrack for Fatale videos Hungry Hearts) with Sundahl on vacation in California
    - Women holding a banner, 1981 (Box 24B, Folder 2)
      Photo slide
    - On Our Backs Christmas Party, 1991 (Box 24B, Folder 3)
      Photos of party organized by Blaire Babora, with guests, contributors, staff
    - Opera Plaza, San Francisco (Box 24B, Folder 4)
      Photos of Susie Bright, Debi Sundahl, Nan Kinney, Honey Lee
    - Debi and Nan (Box 24B, Folder 5)
      Photos at home
    - On Our Backs advertiser (Box 24B, Folder 6)
      Photos of Debi Sundahl, pubic shave out with jewel and paint
    - On Fatale Video Shoot (Box 24B, Folder 7)
      Photo slide of Debi Sundahl and Nan Kinney
    - "Behind Green Doors 2" (Box 24B, Folder 8)
      Photos of the premiere; produced by Mitchell Bros, directed by haron McDonald; Susie Bright and Debi Sundahl were "clothed extras"
    - "Ask Fanny" Snapshots (Box 24B, Folder 9)
      Debi posing with a dildo; "Stormy Leather" catalog shot; by Honey Lee Cottrell
    - Photos of Nan and Debi, 1987 (Box 24B, Folder 10)
      At Baybrick inn and at Palm Springs Divah Shore party
    - Photos at Debi Sundahl's house, ca. 1990 (Box 24B, Folder 11)
      Kat Sunlove; Debi Sundahl, Nina Hartley, Bobbi Lilly
    - AVN Event, "Free Speech Coalition" (Box 24B, Folder 12)
      Photos of Debi Sundahl, Juliet Anderson "Aunt Peg" and 'porn stars'; Los Angeles
    - Tamara at "Lusty Lady", ca. 1985-1986 (Box 24B, Folder 13)
      Photos of dancer and manager of Lustry Lady; Tamara pictured with fiance a week before Tamara died of suicide
    - Post-production Fatale (Box 24B, Folder 14)
      "Safe is Desire" video, Debi Sundahl, Lisa Ginsberg, Icelandic editor
    - Burlezk dancer (Box 24B, Folder 15)
      Dancer came from LUSTY, was on an On Our Backs ad for Burlezk
    - International Ms. Leather, 1987 (Box 24B, Folder 16)
    - International Ms. Leather 2, 1987 (Box 24B, Folder 17)
    - Debi Sundahl National Sexuality Symposium and Expo Plaque, 1993 (Box 24B, Folder 18)
    - Nan Kinney Portraits, 1988 (Box 24B, Folder 19)
    - Burlezk Strip Show (Box 24B, Folder 20)
    - International Ms. Leather 3, 1987 (Box 24B, Folder 21)
    - Stormy Leather photoshoot (Box 24B, Folder 22)
    - "Playboy TV" (Box 24B, Folder 23)
    - Misc. Photos (Box 24B, Folder 24)
    - OOB Christmas Party (Box 24B, Folder 25)
    - Greta Christina from Clips (Box 24B, Folder 26)
    - Nan Kinney and Blaize Bahna (Box 24B, Folder 27)
    - Barbie and Abby Tallmer (Box 24B, Folder 28)
    - Unknown Original (Box 24B, Folder 29)
    - Free Speech Coalition Event (Box 24B, Folder 30)
    - Nan and Debi (Box 24B, Folder 31)
    - OOB Office, Castro SF (Box 24B, Folder 32)
    - Annie Sprinkle's Card Deck of Sex Heroines (Box 24B, Folder 33)
    - Interview with Debi Sundahl (Box 24B, Folder 34)
    - Misc. Nan and Debi (Box 24B, Folder 35)
    - Forum Magazine Photos, 1987 (Box 24B, Folder 36)
    - Nan and Debi's Wedding, 1984-1985 (Box 24B, Folder 37)
    - Burlezk Show (Box 24B, Folder 38)
    - Burlezk Show 2 Continued (Box 24B, Folder 39)
    - San Franciso Gay Day (Box 24B, Folder 40)
    - Aaron's 3rd Grad Photo, 1983 (Box 24B, Folder 41)
    - Virgin Machine Photos (Box 24B, Folder 42)
    - Polaroids of Friends (Box 24B, Folder 43)
    - Jill Posener at the OOB Office, 1985 (Box 24B, Folder 44)
    - "The Virgin Machine" (Box 24B, Folder 45)
    - Christmas party, 1991-1992 (Box 24B, Folder 46)
    - Lesbian Erotic Video-Old Eagle Theater (Box 24B, Folder 47)
    - The End Up Party, 1992 (Box 24B, Folder 48)
    - Lustry Lady by Duroa, 1984 (Box 24B, Folder 49)
    - Debi and nan at home, 1987-1988 (Box 24B, Folder 50)
    - OOB Christmas Party, 1991-1992 (Box 24B, Folder 51)
    - Debi, Nan and Susie's Meeting (Box 24B, Folder 52)
    - "Safe is Desire" publicity photos (Box 24B, Folder 53)
    - Stormy Leather photographs (Box 24B, Folder 54)
    - Debi, Nan and others at an Art Show (Box 24B, Folder 55)
    - Photographs of Susie, Debi and friends (Box 24B, Folder 56)
- Oversize items
  Bright’s collection of prints, drawings and collages, notably drawings by Noreen Scully and works by Honey Lee Cottrell; posters of various films and performances; and images from a variety of photographers.
  - Artwork
    - 1965 Drawing of a clitoris by Hans Bellmer, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Original On Our Backs logo drawing by Norean Scully, Summer 1984 (Box 14, Folder 14)
      Pencil drawing.
      Annotation by Susie: Debi Sundahl commissioned this original drawing to be OOB’s logo. She wanted something Greek and reminiscent of Sappho. This art appeared on the first issue of OOB, Summer 1984. However, we never used it again in print. This was framed and hung in the office for the rest of Debi's 10 year career.
    - Formerly framed Noreen Scully drawing of a female (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Print from Cherry Poptart comic by Larry Welz, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Print of cover and pages from issue No. 1 Signed SPAIN '88.
    - Melinda Gebbie Lost Girls artwork, ca. 1992 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Five signed laminated sheets of artwork from the graphic novel she did with Alan Moore. Items are labeled as Lost Girls, Lost Girls Ch. 1, Lost girls Ch.1 p.4, Lost girls Ch. 2 pg. 1, K.u.K. Militarpost
    - Pencil drawing portrait by Melinda Gebbie, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Matted, signed
    - Cat drawing by Melinda Gebbie (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Signed
    - Black and white drawing of a meal on a table and three pairs of hands by Melinda Gebbie (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Roxie Benefit Series 1982 poster by Melinda Gebbie, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Printing by Red Toad, Design by R. Wilson
    - Two multi colored drawings of male portraits (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Unsigned, probably by Melinda Gebbie.
    - Three black and white prints on heavy paper of a face with other designs (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Three multi colored drawings with text (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Unsigned, probably by Melinda Gebbie. These appear to be drawings that were to be used for posters for the Coyote Point Museum (CuriOdyssey) in San Mateo California.
    - Drawing of a roller skating girl in a street scene (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Probably by Melinda Gebbie.
    - Beamin' Gleamer as A Flash in the Pan poster by Robert Williams., 1971 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Poster is signed by the artist presumably to Melinda Gebbie. "Hey Melinda, Can you make "hide nor hair" of this goddamned thing?!"
    - Black and white print of a topless women and rattle snakes by William Stout, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Hand numbered 206 of 500.
    - The Checkered Demon III untrimmed print by S. Clay Wilson, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      One side is black and white the other is color. Published by Last Gasp.
    - Welcome to the Late Show print by Jay Kinney, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Untrimmed print intended for an album jacket that was never made.
    - Am I My Brother's Keeper? print by unknown artist, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Image of Arite Mitchell and Jim Mitchell. Hand numbered 1 of 5 and signed, signature is illegible.
    - The Smell of the Crowd print by Elizabeth Shaw? Last name illegible (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Hand numbered 18 of 90 and signed. Shows a women with leopards.
    - Photo painting of Susie Bright masturbating with a magic wand vibrator signed by Annie Sprinkle, 2001 (Mapcase-folder 1)
    - Honey Lee Cottrell Diamond Sutra Collage, ca. 1989 (Mapcase-item 2)
      34X25" formerly framed multimedia collage diamond and triangle shaped photos in center, all depicting butch femme lesbian sexuality. The background is mid century sample wallpaper.
      Annotation by Susie: Honey Lee made this piece of art for her and Susie as a couple. It hung in their shared home. She was experimenting with the idea of how you can identify lesbian butch-femme culture at a glance. She was looking at how images of lesbians can portray masculinity while still be recognizable as women and as butch lesbians. Features such as how women touch each other with their hands can flag an image as lesbian. Other signals from clothing include women in uniform, men’s clothing, as well as very femme mid-century burlesque fetish wear. One triangle of the piece features a lesbian cop dressed in uniform; she was one of the role-playing guests Honey Lee arranged to partake in Susie’s 30th birthday party. The triangle photo at the 5 o’clock position on the inset is Honey Lee wearing a tuxedo and evening gloves.
    - Famous Lesbians Collage by Honey Lee Cottrell, ca. 1987 (Mapcase-item 1)
      12 black and white photos of and signed by San Francisco celebrity lesbians mounted collage style on foam core. Clockwise staring in upper left hand corner: Greta Schiller, lesbian filmmaker with her cat; Honey Lee Cottrell, headless nude; Roberta "Birdie" Yuspa, in golden gate park; Rachel Williams, shirtless bent on Susie; Trio of Carla DuBois, Mark Chester and Susie Bright, showing tits; Christian Mann and Susie Bright; Linda Feran aka the "Foosh"; Patt aka Patrick Clafilia; Nan Kinney; Gayle Rubin; Jenni Olsen (Jimmy Dean); Debi Sundahl aka Fanny Fatale.
      Annotation by Susie: All of these photos were shot in San Francisco.
      - Gretta Schuller was the director of Before Stonewall 1984, one of the first films about gay history.
      - Birdi Yuspa was the pioneer researcher in Pulp paperbacks.
      - Rachael Williams was the first Black Ms International Leather, first Black cover model of OOB and a leader of the Black lesbian community.
      - Carla DuBois is a French born dominatrix and fetish pioneer, a leader in the San Francisco leather community and famous for her body work with Fakeir Musafar.
      - Mark Chester is a legendary gay and leather community photographer, the photo of Mark, Carla (aka Mistress Cleo) and Susie was shot at Honey Lee and Susie's house.
      - Christian Mann is a second generation photographer whose father Carl Mann printed some of the first nudist and homoerotic wrestling mags after WWII and ran the influential Catalina gay video and created Video team, which was one of the first gay Black video industries. Christian was SB's mentor and source for a great deal of education on how the porn industry works business wise and legally or illegally as the case requires. During this photoshoot he confided information of illegal activities to Susie and when she asked why he was confiding, he said "because you make these fucking videos" and meant that making videos, breaking several laws, and making them despite prohibition made Susie part of the club.
      - Linda was an aspiring lesbian filmmaker from Austin, who made one lesbian romantic comedy.
      - Pat/Patrick Califia was one of the founders of Samois, author of Saphisty, one of the original contributors to OOB and with Gayle Rubin, one of the best known sexual politics theorists to come out of the lesbian community. She's wearing a leather jacket from Olies (famous lesbian bar post WWII in Oakland).
      - Nan Kinney, cofounder of OOB and Fatale video seated in front of Michele Deloris. Gayle Rubin, Professor of Women's Studies at Ann Arbor, cofounder of samois, early contributor to OOB, legendary sex politics theorist and historian. Photo of Gayle by Honey Lee is the cover of her Anthology Deviations- A Gayle Rubin Reader.
      - Jenni Olsen is former programmer of the SF gay film festival, historic gay film collector and producer, film distributor at Wolfe Video, well known writer on GLBT film and history.
      - Debi Sundahl, cofounder of OOB, Fatale Video. Fanny Fatale is her stage name. Legendary stripper and this photo was taken at the Lesbian Burlezk show which she produced for approx 10 years. In total, shot between '86 and '88, this collection of movers and shakers is a pretty accurate gallery of some of the most influential lesbians and radical sex activists of the period. Out of 14 characters 10 are still highly influential in their field today. Honey Lee made this for Susie and Honey Lee, and was a work of art in the house. It was not exhibited or shown to public during ownership.
  - Posters
    - Lesbians Who... poster by M. Lloyd, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      Woman's Press. Poster is covered with text, sometimes accompanied by small drawings overall. The text varies in size orientation, and style, but usually appears as if handwritten. The text lists many of the various factors that define the lives or identities of lesbians. The more visible instances include: "Lesbians / On / Motorcycles" overlaid on a drawing of a motorcycle, "Lesbian / Firefighters", with a drawing of a female firefighter spraying a fire with a hose, and "Lesbians / With / Brain / Damage".
    - Fete de Femmes event poster (Box 22, Folder 3)
      Association sans but lucratif. Paris.
    - Amazon Reality poster, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      Distributes women's culture, Eugene Oregon.
    - Private Pleasures movie poster, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      Starring Tere and Caerage, Fatale Films, Blush Productions. Poster by Dale Baron.
    - On Our Backs poster, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      Even Femmes Go Down - Morgan Gwenwald. Blush Productions.
    - BurLEZk poster, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      Erotic Danceshow for Women - San Francisco. Blush Productions. Poster features Pepper or Peppar, by Dale Baron. Also a print of the photo used in the poster.
    - Virgin Machine (Die Jungfraeun Maschin) movie poster, 1988 (Mapcase-folder 1)
      Formerly framed. The American release poster from first run of the movie feature Monka Treut staring Susie bright aka Susie Sexpert, Shelly Mars (right) and Ina Blum (left). Elfi Mikech was the producer.
      Annotation by Susie: Monika Treut and her partner Elfi Mcach were German filmakers who came to SF in 87 and were blown away by the lesbian erotic Renaissance scene especially in strip clubs and biker games. Monika vowed to make a feature based on our real lives and came back a second time with a crew and money - no script, just a loose story line, she would direct me with a setup and ask me to improv. Susie's best scene is taking the young virgin to the railroad tracks and showing her a suitcase of dildos. Susie’s other is explaining what the trick is to staying on stage until their 50s.
  - Large Photographs
    Images from a variety of photographers covering a range of subjects. Some may be from On Our Backs, Counter Visions, or Stormy Leather.
    - Collage of photographs of women and text regarding lesbians and S&M. (Box 14, Folder 14)
      Marked for printing, possibly from On Our Backs. Bottom has the letters BDF and MNO.
    - Various photographs of nude and non-nude subjects (Box 14, Folder 14)
      Includes a photo by Honey Lee Cottrell titled "The Year of the Lustfull Lesbian #1" and a photo of and inscribed to Honey Lee Cottrell and Susie Bright by Mark Green
    - Various photographs of non-nude subjects (Box 14, Folder 15)
      Includes photos of Susie Bright, one with peace earrings; a photo of squeezing a grapefruit, titled "Just Squeezed" by Honey Lee Cottrell; Susie Bright in front of a vodka advertisement and sex graffiti, formerly framed photo of Nan Kinney and Debi Sundahl.
    - Vincent (Box 14, Folder 16)
      Collage with photos of a child and images of Amsterdam.
    - Happy 34th Birthday card to Susie Bright (Box 14, Folder 16)
      Card with photo of Susie from Honey Lee Cottrell
    - Large format photographs (Box 22, Folder 2)
      Four photographs including Susie Bright in front of a vodka advertisement and sex graffiti; older women wearing skull face paint; women sitting near snow; and a woman's feet.
- Costumes of Debi Sundahl, ca. 1985
  Costumes worn by Debi Sundahl as Fanny Fatale for the performance of BurLEZk, a lesbian striptease performance, at the Mitchell Bros O’Farrell Theater. The theater was a striptease club at 895 O’Farrell Street near San Francisco’s Tenderloin neighborhood, operated by the pornographers James Lloyd “Jim” Mitchell and Artie Jay Mitchell.
  - Black leather waist belt (Box 15)
    Brand: Stormy Leather
  - Black satin evening gloves pair (Box 15)
    Brand: Satin Lovers
  - Black, rose-bud corset (Box 15)
    Brand: Dominique
  - Archival gloves pair (Box 15)
    Brand: N/A
  - One black leather elbow-length glove (Box 15)
  - Black lace evening gloves pair (Box 15)
  - Black lace blouse (Box 15)
  - Black slip (Box 15)
    Brand: Music Legs
  - Black corset (Box 15)
  - Sheer black scarf (Box 15)
  - Red lace underwear (Box 15)
  - Black brassiere (Box 15)
    Brand: Frederick's
  - Pink garter belt (Box 15)
  - Lace up pink lace camisole (Box 15)
    Brand: Emil Bole, Inc.
  - Black lace leotard (Box 15)
  - White Lace elbow-length gloves pair (Box 15)
  - Red, elbow length globes pair (Box 15)
  - Red sequin strapless top (Box 15)
  - White halter top brassiere (Box 15)
    Brand: Candice Candice
  - White slip skirt (Box 15)
  - Black nylon top (Box 15)
  - Black brassiere (Box 15)
  - Black leather brassiere (Box 15)
  - One breast padding insert (Box 15)
  - White fishnet, thigh-high stockings pair (Box 15)
    Brand: Early Gilbert
  - Black nylon thigh high stockings pair (Box 15)
  - Black nylon thigh high stockings pair (Box 15)
  - Black nylon thigh high stockings pair (Box 15)
    Brand: Berkshire Hosiery
  - Red nylong thong (Box 15)
  - Red netted thong (Box 15)
    Brand: Cosabella
  - Black lace thong (Box 15)
  - Black nylon thong (Box 15)
  - Black heels pair (Box 15)
    Brand: Esprit
- Videos
  Bright’s collection of pornographic videos spanning 1930-2007 as well as recordings of Bright’s news appearances, lectures, award shows and interviews.
  - 1997 Firecracker Alternative Book Awards, 1997; V-6477 (Box 11)
  - Adult Video News Awards 1992, 1992; V-6269 (Box 11)
    Annotation by Susie: "The AVN awards occurred every Jan in Vegas at the consumer electronics shows. They are the Oscars’ of the adult industry. SB was given this in the context of her critic's role at Penthouse "
  - Aerobisex Girls Club, 1986; V-6270 (Box 1)
    Annotation by Susie: "Part of Special group, project or event All Girl Action, lesbian identified Porn stars. All Girl Action. Reviewed in Penthouse Forum Erotic Screen. Following the success of lesbian made video in the early 80s in Northern Cal, a group of out lesbian porn stars and their "dyke daddy" Bruce even decided to make a high energy lesbian video with some of the energetic influence that they had admired in Fatale Video. The piece is phonetic unlike the gentle slower pace of commercial lesbian erotic in the past. There were fisting scenes, but they were cut out. The butches performed in drag. For its time, it was a daring outsider launch for the mainstream biz, and it is the first mainstream release that shows evidence of being influenced by OOB and Fatale. Some of these models were interviewed for OOB. "
  - Aerobisex Girls, 1983; V-6271 (Box 1)
    Annotation by Susie: "This was inspired by the production Jane Fonda exercise of early 80s. Not the pioneer lesbian production. "
  - Afro Erotica, 1986; V-6272 (Box 1)
    Annotation by Susie: "Christian Mann headed up a successful series called Afro Erotics to appeal to a black market and black actors. Distinguished because it promoted black directors and the characters were presented as contemporary LA San Fernando Valley characters, rather than Southern antebellum caricatures. There are still racial cliches but it is a Genx generation point of view. "
  - Afro Erotica vol. 10, 1987; V-6273 (Box 1)